jakjobs.com 2009-12-27

# Privacy Policy | Info Lowongan Kerja Terbaru 2009-2010

## [Privacy Policy](http://jakjobs.com/privacy-policy/ "Privacy Policy")

What follows is the Privacy Statement for [JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/). Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have questions please ask us via our contact info.

**Email Addresses**  
You may choose to add your email address to our contact list via the forms on our websites. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We donÃ¢â‚¬â„¢t currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us via our contact info.

**Ownership of Information**  
[JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/) is the sole owner of any information collected on our websites.

**Cookies**  
Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**  
Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement. [JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/) does not have access to this data.  
We also use third party advertisements on jakjobs.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.jakjobs.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
As a user, you may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google Ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Traffic Reports**  
Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**  
We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but [JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/) may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**  
If [JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/) is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**  
[JakJobs.com](http://jakjobs.com/) websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by JakJobs.com

**Notification of Changes**  
When JakJobs.com makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://www.jakjobs.com/contact-us/).

Best Regards
